[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "You thought I was going to hit you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "thought", "I", "was", "going", "to", "hit", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "I did, actually.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", ",", "actually", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "And I think it's not just me, it's for anyone, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "not", "just", "me", ",", "it", "'s", "for", "anyone", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I mean, you're very honest in the book, and commendably so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "'re", "very", "honest", "in", "the", "book", ",", "and", "commendably", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 62, "question": "I suppose the over riding question for me when I read it was, if you had your time again, would you do the same thing?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "the", "over", "riding", "question", "for", "me", "when", "I", "read", "it", "was", ",", "if", "you", "had", "your", "time", "again", ",", "would", "you", "do", "the", "same", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "As far as like the infidelity stuff, or --", "answer_tokens": ["As", "far", "as", "like", "the", "infidelity", "stuff", ",", "or", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 74, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 75, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Yes, but a proper punch is different, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "a", "proper", "punch", "is", "different", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Yes, I think getting punched in the face by my dad was kind of like, whoa.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "getting", "punched", "in", "the", "face", "by", "my", "dad", "was", "kind", "of", "like", ",", "whoa", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Why was he so angry do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "was", "he", "so", "angry", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Well, I think it was probably learned behavior.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "probably", "learned", "behavior", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Did he ever apologize to you for the hitting?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "he", "ever", "apologize", "to", "you", "for", "the", "hitting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "You think he should?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "he", "should", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "So, you know?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "Your big dream was to be a footballer.", "answer_tokens": ["Your", "big", "dream", "was", "to", "be", "a", "footballer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 173, "question": "When you think back to what you were doing then, do you recognize the man that you were then, a young man?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "think", "back", "to", "what", "you", "were", "doing", "then", ",", "do", "you", "recognize", "the", "man", "that", "you", "were", "then", ",", "a", "young", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 174, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "That they all run a mile (ph)?", "question_tokens": ["That", "they", "all", "run", "a", "mile", "(", "ph", ")", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Oh, yes, totally.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "totally", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "It's not easy, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "easy", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "Well, I was juvenile.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "juvenile", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Tell me how you got into this and realized I can make proper money at this?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "how", "you", "got", "into", "this", "and", "realized", "I", "can", "make", "proper", "money", "at", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, I never did it about the money.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "never", "did", "it", "about", "the", "money", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Janine"]}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Anything else was secondary, you know?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "else", "was", "secondary", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "When you then get remarried to a porn star, Janine, who is abusive to you.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "you", "then", "get", "remarried", "to", "a", "porn", "star", ",", "Janine", ",", "who", "is", "abusive", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "So you were drawn to it?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "were", "drawn", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandra"]}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "And like compared to like something that was chaos, you know, I kind of -- like wow, that's what I need to -- you know, that's the kind of person I need to be with, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "like", "compared", "to", "like", "something", "that", "was", "chaos", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "kind", "of", "--", "like", "wow", ",", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "need", "to", "--", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "the", "kind", "of", "person", "I", "need", "to", "be", "with", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "When you first get together with Sandra, tell me about the early days.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "you", "first", "get", "together", "with", "Sandra", ",", "tell", "me", "about", "the", "early", "days", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Where did you meet her?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "did", "you", "meet", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I met her at the shop.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "met", "her", "at", "the", "shop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Was it love at first sight you think?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "love", "at", "first", "sight", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I think it was for me to a certain extent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "for", "me", "to", "a", "certain", "extent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Like a magnet for gossip?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "a", "magnet", "for", "gossip", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Yes, on a -- I'm like always the guy that like everyone wants to fight.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "on", "a", "--", "I", "'m", "like", "always", "the", "guy", "that", "like", "everyone", "wants", "to", "fight", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "IN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "What were the things that you had in common?", "question_tokens": ["What", "were", "the", "things", "that", "you", "had", "in", "common", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I think, you know, definitely the kids, and our like interests in, you know -- I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", ",", "you", "know", ",", "definitely", "the", "kids", ",", "and", "our", "like", "interests", "in", ",", "you", "know", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "You must have been sure then that this was the one for you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "have", "been", "sure", "then", "that", "this", "was", "the", "one", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "AMES: I was pretty sure.", "answer_tokens": ["AMES", ":", "I", "was", "pretty", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Given everything you've been through before, did you worry that although it all seemed so normal and nice and perfect for you, actually your character, your personality doesn't allow that kind of thing?", "question_tokens": ["Given", "everything", "you", "'ve", "been", "through", "before", ",", "did", "you", "worry", "that", "although", "it", "all", "seemed", "so", "normal", "and", "nice", "and", "perfect", "for", "you", ",", "actually", "your", "character", ",", "your", "personality", "does", "n't", "allow", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I don't think I ever had like a devil on my shoulder or something like that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "ever", "had", "like", "a", "devil", "on", "my", "shoulder", "or", "something", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Because the problem was with me.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "the", "problem", "was", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Yes, but I mean, do you hate yourself for doing that?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "hate", "yourself", "for", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I think I've forgiven myself for what I've done.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "'ve", "forgiven", "myself", "for", "what", "I", "'ve", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Has she forgiven you?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "she", "forgiven", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ":", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Can it be lonely to be that guy?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "it", "be", "lonely", "to", "be", "that", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "I don't know -- well, I think for the -- everything that happens, I'm 100 percent to blame.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "--", "well", ",", "I", "think", "for", "the", "--", "everything", "that", "happens", ",", "I", "'m", "100", "percent", "to", "blame", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Well, what do you think when you hear that back?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "when", "you", "hear", "that", "back", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Well, it just kind of takes me back to that day.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "just", "kind", "of", "takes", "me", "back", "to", "that", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Did she have any inkling about what had been going on?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "have", "any", "inkling", "about", "what", "had", "been", "going", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I think there were some suspicions, you know, which were right on her part.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "were", "some", "suspicions", ",", "you", "know", ",", "which", "were", "right", "on", "her", "part", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "How has she been about the book?", "question_tokens": ["How", "has", "she", "been", "about", "the", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "You don't talk to her at all?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "talk", "to", "her", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Nope.", "answer_tokens": ["Nope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Then it's really nothing?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "it", "'s", "really", "nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to her?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "the", "last", "time", "you", "spoke", "to", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Several months ago.", "answer_tokens": ["Several", "months", "ago", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "How do you know she's forgiven you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "know", "she", "'s", "forgiven", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Well, she told me before that she forgives me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "told", "me", "before", "that", "she", "forgives", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Do you think she understands you better than perhaps other people do?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "she", "understands", "you", "better", "than", "perhaps", "other", "people", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Your current partner?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "current", "partner", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "that", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "I think --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "Have you changed?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "changed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "If people -- I can be the villain, and she'll always be America's sweetheart, you know?", "question_tokens": ["If", "people", "--", "I", "can", "be", "the", "villain", ",", "and", "she", "'ll", "always", "be", "America", "'s", "sweetheart", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "We're going to take another short break.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "going", "to", "take", "another", "short", "break", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "At its absolute worst, what were you going through?", "question_tokens": ["At", "its", "absolute", "worst", ",", "what", "were", "you", "going", "through", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, I think this stuff is just trying to protect the kids, cause I'm a dad first and foremost.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "this", "stuff", "is", "just", "trying", "to", "protect", "the", "kids", ",", "cause", "I", "'m", "a", "dad", "first", "and", "foremost", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Do you care now what they think?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "care", "now", "what", "they", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I couldn't care less, really.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "could", "n't", "care", "less", ",", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Is he a Nazi?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "Nazi", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Nope.", "answer_tokens": ["Nope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Have you ever had Nazi sympathies?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "had", "Nazi", "sympathies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Nothing?", "question_tokens": ["Nothing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Why -- why pose like that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "--", "why", "pose", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "It was a joke.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "You don't collect any Nazi memorabilia?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "collect", "any", "Nazi", "memorabilia", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "JJR", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "So you think that some people might -- might put that together with the picture, and get the wrong idea about you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "think", "that", "some", "people", "might", "--", "might", "put", "that", "together", "with", "the", "picture", ",", "and", "get", "the", "wrong", "idea", "about", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", ":", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I -- I think if you wanted to like point to anything and find some kind of like racism or anti-Semitism or anything, if you really looked at it long enough, you could build up whatever scenario you have.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "think", "if", "you", "wanted", "to", "like", "point", "to", "anything", "and", "find", "some", "kind", "of", "like", "racism", "or", "anti-Semitism", "or", "anything", ",", "if", "you", "really", "looked", "at", "it", "long", "enough", ",", "you", "could", "build", "up", "whatever", "scenario", "you", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "VBN", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 547, "question": "If Sandra is watching this, which she might well be, how would you feel towards her listening to the way that you've talked about her?", "question_tokens": ["If", "Sandra", "is", "watching", "this", ",", "which", "she", "might", "well", "be", ",", "how", "would", "you", "feel", "towards", "her", "listening", "to", "the", "way", "that", "you", "'ve", "talked", "about", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Talked about her, or talked about --", "answer_tokens": ["Talked", "about", "her", ",", "or", "talked", "about", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "What is -- well, Monster what?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "--", "well", ",", "Monster", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", ",", "NNP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Garage we call it in England.", "answer_tokens": ["Garage", "we", "call", "it", "in", "England", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "What do you call it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Garage.", "answer_tokens": ["Garage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Garage or Garage?", "question_tokens": ["Garage", "or", "Garage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Garage actually sounds posher than I said it.", "answer_tokens": ["Garage", "actually", "sounds", "posher", "than", "I", "said", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Is that what you call it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "call", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "I think that's the first time I heard it called that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "the", "first", "time", "I", "heard", "it", "called", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "Are you -- are you allowed to see the child?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "--", "are", "you", "allowed", "to", "see", "the", "child", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "I've never -- never saw him.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "never", "--", "never", "saw", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Since you left?", "question_tokens": ["Since", "you", "left", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "So how long has that been now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "how", "long", "has", "that", "been", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Its been a year.", "answer_tokens": ["Its", "been", "a", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Have you tried to -- to get access?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "tried", "to", "--", "to", "get", "access", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", ":", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "And its been denied to you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "its", "been", "denied", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "On what grounds?", "question_tokens": ["On", "what", "grounds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "I don't know if grounds were given.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "grounds", "were", "given", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Do they ask you why they can't see their little brother?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "ask", "you", "why", "they", "ca", "n't", "see", "their", "little", "brother", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "They -- they do.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "--", "they", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sandra"]}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "You know, hey gone, splitting, separation, you know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "hey", "gone", ",", "splitting", ",", "separation", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "The -- the finality of the picture that you're painting suggests that Sandra -- I mean, you -- you may hope that she's forgiven you.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "--", "the", "finality", "of", "the", "picture", "that", "you", "'re", "painting", "suggests", "that", "Sandra", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "--", "you", "may", "hope", "that", "she", "'s", "forgiven", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 661, "question": "You take pride in that, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "take", "pride", "in", "that", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Well, I kind of thought you deserved it, cause I couldn't get --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "kind", "of", "thought", "you", "deserved", "it", ",", "cause", "I", "could", "n't", "get", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Yes, the -- the first one was for punching a customer.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "the", "--", "the", "first", "one", "was", "for", "punching", "a", "customer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "Did you get freebies then?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "freebies", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "You love your tattoos, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "love", "your", "tattoos", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "I -- I like them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "like", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 698, "question": "Are -- are you engaged?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "--", "are", "you", "engaged", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 699, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 700, "question": "Are -- are you married, cause you got a wedding ring on?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "--", "are", "you", "married", ",", "cause", "you", "got", "a", "wedding", "ring", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 701, "answer": "Well, she got me a ring made, and -- and gave it to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "got", "me", "a", "ring", "made", ",", "and", "--", "and", "gave", "it", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "When are you planning to get married?", "question_tokens": ["When", "are", "you", "planning", "to", "get", "married", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "This is number four, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "number", "four", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "CD", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ":"], "qSentId": 715, "question": "And you know, she's just awesome, you know?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "know", ",", "she", "'s", "just", "awesome", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "Do you think you may --", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "may", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Do you believe you may have found true love?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "you", "may", "have", "found", "true", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "What's your point?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "What does she do for a living?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "she", "do", "for", "a", "living", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "Movie star, actor.", "answer_tokens": ["Movie", "star", ",", "actor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "An actor.", "answer_tokens": ["An", "actor", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", ":", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 752, "question": "You think it was an act?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "it", "was", "an", "act", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 753, "answer": "I -- I think you know, that whole -- that, you know, people that have to live in that world, and -- and --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "think", "you", "know", ",", "that", "whole", "--", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "people", "that", "have", "to", "live", "in", "that", "world", ",", "and", "--", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 754, "question": "Are you glad to be out of it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "glad", "to", "be", "out", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 755, "answer": "Man -- 100 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["Man", "--", "100", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110513pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "Is that what you're saying?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "'re", "saying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "It's just pretend.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "pretend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]